

HUGO PEREIRA

ABOUT ME

Hard-working and passionate IT business analyst with one year of experience in the banking area, evaluating and improving regulatory systems for Natixis in Portugal, meeting business requests through Agile and Scrum methodologies. Organized, communicative and quick-to-learn person, with capacity and experience to work as team, with self-initiative and critical spirit to reach positive results and implement technological solutions.

CONTACT

Phone: (+351) 911 775 364

Email: hugopm2000@gmail.com

Location: Vila do Conde, Porto

Date of birth: 06/07/2000

Driving license: B

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/hugo-

<u>pereira-89919a218</u>

SKILLS

Excel, Google Sheets • • • • •

PowerBl, Tableau • • • • • •

Python • • • • •

SQL ••••

R ••••

Microsoft Access • • • •

WORK EXPERIENCE

Logistic operator | Consoveyo, Maia

JUN. 2019 - SET. 2019

- · Warehouse maintenance;
- · Space management and packaging;
- · Controls on flow of goods;
- · Balance sheet activities (inventory).

Client manager | Alameda Créditos - Intermediário de Crédito, Vila do Conde (Summer internship)

JUL. 2021 - SET. 2021

- · Presentation of credit proposals to consumers;
- · Consultancy service, through personalized recommendations on credit proposals;
- IT Business Analyst | Natixis, Porto (Internship)

NOV. 2022 - PRESENT

- Analysis and study of current and new Transaction Regulatory Reports (EMIR)
- · Creation and update of appropriate documentation;
- · Identify gaps in different processes making improvement iniciative across the business and the
- Provide support to different users on investment banking regulatory issues (Sophis Equities and Sophis Commodities) for different Transaction Regulatory Reports (MIFID, EMIR, SFTR):

EDUCATION

 Bachelor in Economics | University Trás-os-Montes e Alto Douro, Vila Real

SET. 2018 - JUN. 2021

Bachelor in Economics University SGGW – Warsaw University of Life Sciences

FEV. 2020 - JUN. 2020

Bachelor in Business Management| University Trás-os-Montes e Alto Douro, Vila Real

SET. 2021 - PRESENT

EXTRA-CURRICULAR TRAININGS

- · English certificate C1 from Wall Street English;
- Training with "Business English Course" certificate;
- · Professional Excel training with certificate;
- · Professional course "Google Data Analytics".